

Adrian

♦ Web Developer

CONTACT

+40757734760

adrianxfilip@gmail.com

adrianxfilip.github.io/personal-page

Sighisoara, România

SKILLS



HTML



SASS



JavaScript



React



Redux



Node



Express



MongoDB





Socket.IO



git

Mongoose

GIT

ABOUT ME

Experienced web developer, adept in all stages of web development.

Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting. Always willing to take on any task, I'm at my best when I'm being challenged.

EXPERIENCE

SCRIPTWRITER

at Ipsos.

Aug. 2022 - Present

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER

Remote.

Feb. 2022 - Aug. 2022

TECH SUPPORT SPECIALIST

at CGS Romania.

Aug. 2021 - Feb. 2022

EDUCATION

COMPUTER ENGINEERING

at Universitatea "Lucian Blaga" din Sibiu.

Sibiu, Romania 2020 - 2021

INFORMATHICS

at Liceul Teoretic "Joseph Haltrich".

Sighisoara, Romania 2016 - 2020

HOBBIES









LANGUAGES

Romanian Native

English
CEFR Level C2

CERTIFICATES

All freeCodeCamp certificates are available at freecodecamp.org/adrianfilip

Responsive Web Design Certification freeCodeCamp.

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Certification freeCodeCamp.

Front End Development Libraries Certification freeCodeCamp.

Back End Development and APIs Certification freeCodeCamp.

Programming Certificate
Liceul Teoretic "Joseph Haltrich" Sighisoara

Cambridge English Level 3 | CEFR Level C2 Certificate Cambridge English.

PROJECTS

PERSONAL PAGE

adrianxfilip.github.io/personal-page

Portofolio website with some more info about myself and my projects

CAR LOTTERY

adrianxfilip.github.io/getaticket

Website devolped for a car lottery. Project was done as a proof of concept, while also being a great challange and opportunity to improve my skills.

COINFLIP GAME

adrianxfilip.github.io/coinflip-client

Casino style coin flipping game developed using React and Socket.IO

MULTIPLE PROJECTS

Various projects required for earning my freeCodeCamp certifications

Projects are available at:

- freecodecamp org/adrianfilip
- codepen.io/adrianfilip663
- replit.com/@AdrianFilip